<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sustainable Innovation on Social Architecture</title>
    <link>/tags/sustainable-innovation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sustainable Innovation on Social Architecture</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/sustainable-innovation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SHAU Rotterdam-Bandung</title>
      <link>/post/shau/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/shau/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Bima Microlibrary Location: Bandung, Indonesia Date Designed: 2015
Date Completed: 2016
Size: 160 sqm
Client: Dompet Dhuafa, City of Bandung
Programme: Education ABOUT SHAU
SHAU (Rotterdam-Bandung) was established in 2009 by married partners, Florian Heinzelmann and Deliana Suryawinata, as two independent offices in Rotterdam and Munich and serves as common platform. Since 2012, SHAU has been running its office in Indonesia; first in Jakarta and currently in Bandung.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MASS Design Group</title>
      <link>/post/mass_design_group/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/mass_design_group/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Renovation of Ruhehe Primary School Location: Ruhengeri (or Musanze), Rwanda Date Designed: 2015
Date Completed: 2018 Size: 560 sqm
Client: Musanze District Ministry of Education Programme: Education MASS Design Group
MASS consists of a team of over 120+ architects, landscape architects, engineers, builders, furniture designers, writers, filmmakers, and researchers representing 20 countries across the globe. They believe in expanding access to design that is purposeful, healing, and hopeful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ground Up Initiative</title>
      <link>/post/gui/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gui/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Kampung Kampus Location: Singapore, Singapore Date Designed: 2009 Date Completed: In Progress Size: 26,000 sqm
Client: Goverment Organisations, Local Community, Nee Soon Residents, Leadership and Training Groups Programme: Education ABOUT Ground Up Initiative
Ground-Up Initiative (GUI) is a non-profit community, guided by the spirit of innovation, resilience and grounded leadership to demonstrate urban sustainability. ABOUT Kampung Kampus
Ground-Up Initiative (GUI) is a non-profit community, guided by the spirit of innovation, resilience and grounded leadership to demonstrate urban sustainability.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>