<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sustainable Innovation on Social Architecture</title>
    <link>/tags/sustainable-innovation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sustainable Innovation on Social Architecture</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/sustainable-innovation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Studio Anna Heringer</title>
      <link>/post/studio_anna_heringer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/studio_anna_heringer/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: METI Handmade School Location: Rudrapur, Dinajpur district, Bangladesh Date Designed: 2005
Date Completed: 2006
Size: 325 sqm
Client: Modern Education and Training Institute
Programme: Education ABOUT Studio Anna Heringer
Studio Anna Heringer is headed by Anna Heringer herself, who is a German Architect who strongly advocates for the use of bamboo and mud as ‘sustainable’ materials for construction. Although these materials are considered ‘low-class’ in the building industry, Anna believes that they are not inferior in their properties and pioneered the utilisation of these resources in community-driven architectural projects in Bangladesh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHAU Rotterdam-Bandung</title>
      <link>/post/shau/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/shau/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Bima Microlibrary Location: Bandung, Indonesia Date Designed: 2015
Date Completed: 2016
Size: 160 sqm
Client: Dompet Dhuafa, City of Bandung
Programme: Education ABOUT SHAU
SHAU (Rotterdam-Bandung) was established in 2009 by married partners, Florian Heinzelmann and Deliana Suryawinata, as two independent offices in Rotterdam and Munich and serves as common platform. Since 2012, SHAU has been running its office in Indonesia; first in Jakarta and currently in Bandung.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MASS Design Group</title>
      <link>/post/mass_design_group/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/mass_design_group/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Renovation of Ruhehe Primary School Location: Ruhengeri (or Musanze), Rwanda Date Designed: 2015
Date Completed: 2018 Size: 560 sqm
Client: Musanze District Ministry of Education Programme: Education MASS Design Group
MASS consists of a team of over 120+ architects, landscape architects, engineers, builders, furniture designers, writers, filmmakers, and researchers representing 20 countries across the globe. They believe in expanding access to design that is purposeful, healing, and hopeful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ground Up Initiative</title>
      <link>/post/gui/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gui/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Kampung Kampus Location: Singapore, Singapore Date Designed: 2009 Date Completed: In Progress Size: 26,000 sqm
Client: Goverment Organisations, Local Community, Nee Soon Residents, Leadership and Training Groups Programme: Education ABOUT Ground Up Initiative
Ground-Up Initiative (GUI) is a non-profit community, guided by the spirit of innovation, resilience and grounded leadership to demonstrate urban sustainability. ABOUT Kampung Kampus
Ground-Up Initiative (GUI) is a non-profit community, guided by the spirit of innovation, resilience and grounded leadership to demonstrate urban sustainability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VTN Architects</title>
      <link>/post/vtn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/vtn/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Farming Kindergarten Location: Dongnai, Vietnam Date Designed: 2012
Date Completed: 2013
Size: 3,800 sqm Client: Pou Chen Vietnam
Programme: Education ABOUT VTN Architects
VTN Architects is a well-known architectural firm in Vietnam, with two branches, located in Hanoi and Ho Chi Mihn city. The firm mainly focuses on cultural, residential, and commercial projects for both local and international clients.
Vo Trong Nghia, an architectural graduate from University of Tokyo, founded VTN Architects in 2006.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>