<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Education on Social Architecture</title>
    <link>/tags/education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Education on Social Architecture</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Studio Anna Heringer</title>
      <link>/post/studio_anna_heringer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/studio_anna_heringer/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: METI Handmade School Location: Rudrapur, Dinajpur district, Bangladesh Date Designed: 2005
Date Completed: 2006
Size: 325 sqm
Client: Modern Education and Training Institute
Programme: Education ABOUT Studio Anna Heringer
Studio Anna Heringer is headed by Anna Heringer herself, a German Architect who strongly advocates for the use of mud and bamboo as sustainable materials for construction. Although these materials are considered ‘low-class’ in the building industry, Anna believes that they are not inferior in their properties and pioneered the utilisation of these resources in communitydriven architectural projects in Bangladesh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VTN Architects</title>
      <link>/post/vtn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/vtn/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Farming Kindergarten Location: Dongnai, Vietnam Date Designed: 2012
Date Completed: 2013
Size: 3,800 sqm Client: Pou Chen Vietnam
Programme: Education ABOUT VTN Architects
VTN Architects is a well-known architectural firm in Vietnam, with two branches, located in Hanoi and Ho Chi Mihn city. The firm mainly focuses on cultural, residential, and commercial projects for both local and international clients. Vo Trong Nghia, an architectural graduate from University of Tokyo, founded VTN Architects in 2006.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAUKIN Studio</title>
      <link>/post/caukin_studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/caukin_studio/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Naidi Community Hall Location: Vanua Levu, Fiji Date Designed: 2018
Date Completed: 2018
Size: 130 sqm
Client: Naqaqa Giving Foundation
Programme: Public Space ABOUT CAUKIN Studio
CAUKIN Studio approaches architecture as a tool of empowerment that every individual and community should have equal access to. The organisation’s take on social architecture seeks to create better quality spaces for marginalised communities by minimising the economic barriers involved in the undertaking of such projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>