<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rural Revitalisation on Social Architecture</title>
    <link>/tags/rural-revitalisation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rural Revitalisation on Social Architecture</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/rural-revitalisation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Atelier-3</title>
      <link>/post/atelier-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/atelier-3/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Nepal Rebuilt House Location: Katunje, Dahding Besi, Nepal Date Designed: 2016
Date Completed: In Progress
Size: 60 sqm
Client: Future Village Foundation &amp;amp; IDEA Foundation
Programme: Residential ABOUT Atelier-3
Atelier-3 &amp;amp; Design For People Co. has been a leading force in developing and promoting sustainable lightweight steel houses in rural &amp;amp; ethnic areas since 1999. The main goal of the practice is to improve the infrastructure and living environment of the rural area, leading to sustainable development as well as an ecological society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAUKIN Studio</title>
      <link>/post/caukin_studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/caukin_studio/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Naidi Community Hall Location: Vanua Levu, Fiji Date Designed: 2018
Date Completed: 2018
Size: 130 sqm
Client: Naqaqa Giving Foundation
Programme: Public Space ABOUT CAUKIN Studio
CAUKIN Studio approaches architecture as a tool of empowerment that every individual and community should have equal access to. The organisation’s take on social architecture seeks to create better quality spaces for marginalised communities by minimising the economic barriers involved in the undertaking of such projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DnA_Design and Architecture</title>
      <link>/post/dna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/dna/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Brown Sugar Factory Location: Xing Village, China Date Designed: 2015
Date Completed: 2016
Size: 1,230 sqm
Client: Government of Zhangxi Village, Songyang County
Programme: Culture ABOUT DnA_Design and Architecture
DnA_Design and Architect is an interdisciplinary practice engaged in public buildings, architectural planning, landscape design, and cultural institutions. The studio aims to address contemporary living environments in both physical and social at various scales. DnA_Design and Architecture has done many successful projects, including Brown Sugar Factory, Wang Jing Memorial Hall, Chinese Herbal Garden, and Toufu Factory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IX Architects</title>
      <link>/post/ix_architects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ix_architects/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: More than just a Library Location: Siem Reap, Cambodia Date Designed: 2017 Date Completed: 2018 Size: 26,500 sqm
Client: Östersund Municipality, Diös Programme: Culture ABOUT IX Architects
IX Architects Pte Ltd (IXA) is a corporatized architectural practice registered with the Board of Architects, Singapore. IXA is also listed under the panel of Consultant for Public Sector projects with the Building and Construction Authority. From our humble beginnings in 2004, we are now a well-established and recognized regional architectural practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MASS Design Group</title>
      <link>/post/mass_design_group/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/mass_design_group/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Renovation of Ruhehe Primary School Location: Ruhengeri (or Musanze), Rwanda Date Designed: 2015
Date Completed: 2018 Size: 560 sqm
Client: Musanze District Ministry of Education Programme: Education MASS Design Group
MASS consists of a team of over 120+ architects, landscape architects, engineers, builders, furniture designers, writers, filmmakers, and researchers representing 20 countries across the globe. They believe in expanding access to design that is purposeful, healing, and hopeful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHAU</title>
      <link>/post/shau/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/shau/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Bima Microlibrary Location: Bandung, Indonesia Date Designed: 2015
Date Completed: 2016
Size: 160 sqm
Client: Dompet Dhuafa, City of Bandung
Programme: Education ABOUT SHAU
SHAU (Rotterdam-Bandung) was established in 2009 by married partners, Florian Heinzelmann and Deliana Suryawinata, as two independent offices in Rotterdam and Munich and serves as common platform. Since 2012, SHAU has been running its office in Indonesia; first in Jakarta and currently in Bandung.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Studio Anna Heringer</title>
      <link>/post/studio_anna_heringer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/studio_anna_heringer/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: METI Handmade School Location: Rudrapur, Dinajpur district, Bangladesh Date Designed: 2005
Date Completed: 2006
Size: 325 sqm
Client: Modern Education and Training Institute
Programme: Education ABOUT Studio Anna Heringer
Studio Anna Heringer is headed by Anna Heringer herself, who is a German Architect who strongly advocates for the use of bamboo and mud as ‘sustainable’ materials for construction. Although these materials are considered ‘low-class’ in the building industry, Anna believes that they are not inferior in their properties and pioneered the utilisation of these resources in community-driven architectural projects in Bangladesh.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>