<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Social Architecture</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Social Architecture</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Architecture 2020 — Theory and Practice</title>
      <link>/post/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/about/</guid>
      <description>Social Architecture — Theory and Practice aims to equip the students with theoretical/historical knowledge of ‘Social Architecture’ as well as practical skills for practicing it. Students will be exposed to key concepts, methods and goals developed in social architecture, an umbrella term that includes community architecture and planning, community design, social design, democratic design, community development, etc. which share a common approach of environmental design that encourages social behaviors leading towards certain public benefits, such as livability, safety, and sustainability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Map</title>
      <link>/post/map/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/map/</guid>
      <description>{&#34;x&#34;:{&#34;options&#34;:{&#34;crs&#34;:{&#34;crsClass&#34;:&#34;L.CRS.EPSG3857&#34;,&#34;code&#34;:null,&#34;proj4def&#34;:null,&#34;projectedBounds&#34;:null,&#34;options&#34;:{}}},&#34;calls&#34;:[{&#34;method&#34;:&#34;addProviderTiles&#34;,&#34;args&#34;:[&#34;Stamen.Toner&#34;,null,null,{&#34;errorTileUrl&#34;:&#34;&#34;,&#34;noWrap&#34;:false,&#34;detectRetina&#34;:false}]},{&#34;method&#34;:&#34;addCircleMarkers&#34;,&#34;args&#34;:[[37.5641134,-16.8006309,51.5611976,1.3167354,63.1757722,39.9386949,14.602861,27.9110176,-1.4918885,22.3193039,28.495075,53.3924013,-6.909758,41.9433816,1.3505428,28.312001,1.4142648,25.6346367,10.7872729],[140.1078445,179.3618146,-0.0928437,103.8388212,14.639316,116.417661,121.045855,84.8919664,29.5571677,114.1693611,119.401878,-2.9558926,107.591709,-87.6946043,103.7076413,109.738781,103.8279127,88.583867,106.7498105],12,null,null,{&#34;interactive&#34;:true,&#34;className&#34;:&#34;&#34;,&#34;stroke&#34;:true,&#34;color&#34;:&#34;#E7451F&#34;,&#34;weight&#34;:0,&#34;opacity&#34;:0.5,&#34;fill&#34;:true,&#34;fillColor&#34;:&#34;#E7451F&#34;,&#34;fillOpacity&#34;:0.5},null,null,[&#34;Project Name&amp;emsp;Hajimari Art Center&amp;emsp;Firm&amp;emsp;studio-L&amp;emsp;Keywords&amp;emsp;Citizen Participation, Empowerment, Art Brut, Social Welfare&amp;emsp;Country&amp;emsp;Japan&amp;emsp;Details&amp;emsp;Click Here&amp;emsp;&#34;,&#34;Project Name&amp;emsp;Naidi Community Hall&amp;emsp;Firm&amp;emsp;CAUKIN Studio&amp;emsp;Keywords&amp;emsp;Democratic education, Quality Design, Accessibility for All, Community Focused, Sustainable Innovation&amp;emsp;Country&amp;emsp;Fiji&amp;emsp;Details&amp;emsp;Click Here&amp;emsp;&#34;,&#34;Project Name&amp;emsp;Kings Crescent Estate&amp;emsp;Firm&amp;emsp;Muf Architecture + Art&amp;emsp;Keywords&amp;emsp;Citizen Participation, Empowerment&amp;emsp;Country&amp;emsp;United Kingdom&amp;emsp;Details&amp;emsp;Click Here&amp;emsp;&#34;,&#34;Project Name&amp;emsp;Hack Our Play - St. James Church Kindergarten&amp;emsp;Firm&amp;emsp;Participate in Design (P!D)&amp;emsp;Keywords&amp;emsp;Citizen Participation&amp;emsp;Country&amp;emsp;Singapore&amp;emsp;Details&amp;emsp;Click Here&amp;emsp;&#34;,&#34;Project Name&amp;emsp;Cultural Block Östersund&amp;emsp;Firm&amp;emsp;Kjellander Sjöberg&amp;emsp;Keywords&amp;emsp;Participatory Design in Cultural Centre&amp;emsp;Country&amp;emsp;Sweden&amp;emsp;Details&amp;emsp;Click Here&amp;emsp;&#34;,&#34;Project Name&amp;emsp;Leping Social Entrepreneur Foundation Headquarter&amp;emsp;Firm&amp;emsp;People&#39;s Architecture Office&amp;emsp;Keywords&amp;emsp;People, Social wellbeing Collaboration, Integration&amp;emsp;Country&amp;emsp;China&amp;emsp;Details&amp;emsp;Click Here&amp;emsp;&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atelier-3</title>
      <link>/post/atelier-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/atelier-3/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Nepal Rebuilt House Location: Katunje, Dahding Besi, Nepal Date Designed: 2016
Date Completed: In Progress
Size: 60 sqm
Client: Future Village Foundation &amp;amp; IDEA Foundation
Programme: Residential ABOUT Atelier-3
Atelier-3 &amp;amp; Design For People Co. has been a leading force in developing and promoting sustainable lightweight steel houses in rural &amp;amp; ethnic areas since 1999. The main goal of the practice is to improve the infrastructure and living environment of the rural area, leading to sustainable development as well as an ecological society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BillionBricks</title>
      <link>/post/billion_bricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/billion_bricks/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: powerHYDE Location: Konchur Karnataka, India Date Designed: 2019
Date Completed: In Progress
Size: 34,000 sqm sqm
Client: - Programme: Residential ABOUT billionBricks
Housing is a basic necessity and a human right, the ﬁrst step of empowerment towards emerging out of poverty. Co-founders of billionBricks Prasoon Kumar and Anurag Srivastava envisions “a world where no one is homeless, and where everyone has access to opportunities for economic and social upliftment” (Rebel, 10 Restorative Innovation Initiatives from Singapore You Should Know 2018).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAUKIN Studio</title>
      <link>/post/caukin_studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/caukin_studio/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Naidi Community Hall Location: Vanua Levu, Fiji Date Designed: 2018
Date Completed: 2018
Size: 130 sqm
Client: Naqaqa Giving Foundation
Programme: Public Space ABOUT CAUKIN Studio
CAUKIN Studio approaches architecture as a tool of empowerment that every individual and community should have equal access to. The organisation’s take on social architecture seeks to create better quality spaces for marginalised communities by minimising the economic barriers involved in the undertaking of such projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DnA_Design and Architecture</title>
      <link>/post/dna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/dna/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Brown Sugar Factory Location: Xing Village, China Date Designed: 2015
Date Completed: 2016
Size: 1,230 sqm
Client: Government of Zhangxi Village, Songyang County
Programme: Culture ABOUT DnA_Design and Architecture
DnA_Design and Architect is an interdisciplinary practice engaged in public buildings, architectural planning, landscape design, and cultural institutions. The studio aims to address contemporary living environments in both physical and social at various scales. DnA_Design and Architecture has done many successful projects, including Brown Sugar Factory, Wang Jing Memorial Hall, Chinese Herbal Garden, and Toufu Factory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ground Up Initiative</title>
      <link>/post/gui/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gui/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Kampung Kampus Location: Singapore, Singapore Date Designed: 2009 Date Completed: In Progress Size: 26,000 sqm
Client: Goverment Organisations, Local Community, Nee Soon Residents, Leadership and Training Groups Programme: Education ABOUT Ground Up Initiative
Ground-Up Initiative (GUI) is a non-profit community, guided by the spirit of innovation, resilience and grounded leadership to demonstrate urban sustainability. ABOUT Kampung Kampus
Ground-Up Initiative (GUI) is a non-profit community, guided by the spirit of innovation, resilience and grounded leadership to demonstrate urban sustainability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IX Architects</title>
      <link>/post/ix_architects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ix_architects/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: More than just a Library Location: Siem Reap, Cambodia Date Designed: 2017 Date Completed: 2018 Size: 26,500 sqm
Client: Östersund Municipality, Diös Programme: Culture ABOUT IX Architects
IX Architects Pte Ltd (IXA) is a corporatized architectural practice registered with the Board of Architects, Singapore. IXA is also listed under the panel of Consultant for Public Sector projects with the Building and Construction Authority. From our humble beginnings in 2004, we are now a well-established and recognized regional architectural practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kjellander Sjöberg</title>
      <link>/post/kjellander_sjoberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/kjellander_sjoberg/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Cultural Block Östersund Location: Östersund, Sweden Date Designed: 2017
Date Completed: In Progress Size: 26,500 sqm
Client: Östersund Municipality Programme: Public Space ABOUT Kjellander Sjöberg
Kjellander Sjöberg is based in Stockholm, Sweden and provides architectural and urban design services in the Nordic countries. Established in 1998, it is currently a multi-nationality medium-sized office led by partners Ola Kjellander, Stefan Sjöberg, Mi Inkinen and Lena Viterstedt. Kjellander Sjöberg believes that the built environment influences social progress, quality of life and cultural richness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MASS Design Group</title>
      <link>/post/mass_design_group/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/mass_design_group/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Renovation of Ruhehe Primary School Location: Ruhengeri (or Musanze), Rwanda Date Designed: 2015
Date Completed: 2018 Size: 560 sqm
Client: Musanze District Ministry of Education Programme: Education MASS Design Group
MASS consists of a team of over 120+ architects, landscape architects, engineers, builders, furniture designers, writers, filmmakers, and researchers representing 20 countries across the globe. They believe in expanding access to design that is purposeful, healing, and hopeful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Bite Design Studio</title>
      <link>/post/one_bite_studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/one_bite_studio/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Project House Location: Sham Shui Po/Wan Chai/Aberdeen, Hong Kong Date Designed: 2017
Date Completed: In Progress Size: Depending on Vacant Shop
Client: Private Programme: Institution ABOUT One Bite Design Studio
One Bite is a creative team of strategists, architects, designers, community outreach managers and event managers. Headquartered in Hong Kong with an office in Singapore, the firm has been involved in various architectural, interior design; art and pop-up installations; visual communication and social creative projects in Hong Kong and Southeast Asia since 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Participate in Design (P!D)</title>
      <link>/post/pid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pid/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Hack Our Play - St. James Church Kindergarten Location: Singapore, Singapore Date Designed: 2017 Date Completed: 2017 Size: 128 sqm
Client: St. James Church Kindergarten Programme: Public Space ABOUT P!D
Participate in Design (P!D) is a non-profit design, planning and educational organisation that provides their expertise in participa- tory design to help institutions in Singapore design community-owned spaces and solu- tions. P!D was founded in 2013 by founders, Jan Lim and Mizah Rahman with the vision to spread the ideas of participatory design across Singapore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People&#39;s Architecture Office</title>
      <link>/post/pao/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pao/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Leping Social Entrepreneur Foundation Headquarter
Location: Beijing, China
Date Designed: -
Date Completed: - Size: - sqm
Client: - Programme: Institution ABOUT People’s Architecture Office
Beijing-based People’s Architecture Office (PAO) / People’s Industrial Design Office (PIDO) was founded by He Zhe, James Shen and Zang Feng in 2010, and consists of a multi-disciplinary team of architects, engineers, product designers and urbanists. With the belief that design is for the masses the studio focuses on social impact through design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAA Architects</title>
      <link>/post/saa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/saa/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: St Josephs’ Nursing Home Location: Singapore, Singapore Date Designed: - Date Completed: 2017 Size: 22,022 sqm Client: Catholic Welfare Services Singapore Programme: Healthcare ABOUT SAA Architects
SAA is a leading full-service architecture practice headquartered in Singapore. With over 50 years of design and built expertise, they are committed to the pursuit of excellence in the design and delivery of people-oriented architecture that connects communities with their urban environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHAU</title>
      <link>/post/shau/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/shau/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Bima Microlibrary Location: Bandung, Indonesia Date Designed: 2015
Date Completed: 2016
Size: 160 sqm
Client: Dompet Dhuafa, City of Bandung
Programme: Education ABOUT SHAU
SHAU (Rotterdam-Bandung) was established in 2009 by married partners, Florian Heinzelmann and Deliana Suryawinata, as two independent offices in Rotterdam and Munich and serves as common platform. Since 2012, SHAU has been running its office in Indonesia; first in Jakarta and currently in Bandung.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Studio Anna Heringer</title>
      <link>/post/studio_anna_heringer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/studio_anna_heringer/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: METI Handmade School Location: Rudrapur, Dinajpur district, Bangladesh Date Designed: 2005
Date Completed: 2006
Size: 325 sqm
Client: Modern Education and Training Institute
Programme: Education ABOUT Studio Anna Heringer
Studio Anna Heringer is headed by Anna Heringer herself, who is a German Architect who strongly advocates for the use of bamboo and mud as ‘sustainable’ materials for construction. Although these materials are considered ‘low-class’ in the building industry, Anna believes that they are not inferior in their properties and pioneered the utilisation of these resources in community-driven architectural projects in Bangladesh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>studio-L</title>
      <link>/post/studio_l/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/studio_l/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Hajimari Art Center Location: Inawashiro, Japan Date Designed: 2013 Date Completed: 2014 Size: 1,217.14 sqm (Site area), 235.66 sqm (Building area), 284.01 sqm (Total floor area) Client: Asaka Hospital Group Programme: Culture ABOUT studio-L
Studio L is a Japanese firm that focues on community design. As community designers, the firm focuses on empowering the local people to participate in problem solving in their neighbourhoods. A typical workflow of a project consists of researching on case studies, conducting interviews and workshops as well as connecting different people in the local community to be involved in the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WTA Architecture and Design Studio</title>
      <link>/post/wta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/wta/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Book Stop Project Location: Manila, Philippines Date Designed: 2016
Date Completed: 2016
Size: 12 sqm
Client: -
Programme: Education ABOUT WTA Architecture and Design
WTA Architecture and Design Studio is one of the Top 10 Architectural Firms in the Philippines in 2018 as cited by BCI Asia. It is a multidisciplinary group of young and idealistic architects, interior designers, urban planners and engineers based in Manila, Philippines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VTN Architects</title>
      <link>/post/vtn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/vtn/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Farming Kindergarten Location: Dongnai, Vietnam Date Designed: 2012
Date Completed: 2013
Size: 3,800 sqm Client: Pou Chen Vietnam
Programme: Education ABOUT VTN Architects
VTN Architects is a well-known architectural firm in Vietnam, with two branches, located in Hanoi and Ho Chi Mihn city. The firm mainly focuses on cultural, residential, and commercial projects for both local and international clients.
Vo Trong Nghia, an architectural graduate from University of Tokyo, founded VTN Architects in 2006.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>