<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ownership on Social Architecture</title>
    <link>/tags/ownership/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ownership on Social Architecture</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/ownership/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SHAU Rotterdam-Bandung</title>
      <link>/post/shau/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/shau/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Bima Microlibrary Location: Bandung, Indonesia Date Designed: 2015
Date Completed: 2016
Size: 160 sqm
Client: Dompet Dhuafa, City of Bandung
Programme: Education ABOUT SHAU
SHAU (Rotterdam-Bandung) was established in 2009 by married partners, Florian Heinzelmann and Deliana Suryawinata, as two independent offices in Rotterdam and Munich and serves as common platform. Since 2012, SHAU has been running its office in Indonesia; first in Jakarta and currently in Bandung.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kjellander Sjöberg</title>
      <link>/post/kjellander_sjoberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/kjellander_sjoberg/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Cultural Block Östersund Location: Östersund, Sweden Date Designed: 2017
Date Completed: In Progress Size: 26,500 sqm
Client: Östersund Municipality Programme: Public Space ABOUT Kjellander Sjöberg
Kjellander Sjöberg is based in Stockholm, Sweden and provides architectural and urban design services in the Nordic countries. Established in 1998, it is currently a multi-nationality medium-sized office led by partners Ola Kjellander, Stefan Sjöberg, Mi Inkinen and Lena Viterstedt. Kjellander Sjöberg believes that the built environment influences social progress, quality of life and cultural richness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ground Up Initiative</title>
      <link>/post/gui/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gui/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Kampung Kampus Location: Singapore, Singapore Date Designed: 2009 Date Completed: In Progress Size: 26,000 sqm
Client: Goverment Organisations, Local Community, Nee Soon Residents, Leadership and Training Groups Programme: Education ABOUT Ground Up Initiative
Ground-Up Initiative (GUI) is a non-profit community, guided by the spirit of innovation, resilience and grounded leadership to demonstrate urban sustainability. ABOUT Kampung Kampus
Ground-Up Initiative (GUI) is a non-profit community, guided by the spirit of innovation, resilience and grounded leadership to demonstrate urban sustainability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Participate in Design (P!D)</title>
      <link>/post/pid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pid/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Hack Our Play - St. James Church Kindergarten Location: Singapore, Singapore Date Designed: 2017 Date Completed: 2017 Size: 128 sqm
Client: St. James Church Kindergarten Programme: Public Space ABOUT P!D
Participate in Design (P!D) is a non-profit design, planning and educational organisation that provides their expertise in participa- tory design to help institutions in Singapore design community-owned spaces and solu- tions. P!D was founded in 2013 by founders, Jan Lim and Mizah Rahman with the vision to spread the ideas of participatory design across Singapore.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>