<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Urban Revitalisation on Social Architecture</title>
    <link>/tags/urban-revitalisation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Urban Revitalisation on Social Architecture</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/urban-revitalisation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WTA Architecture and Design Studio</title>
      <link>/post/wta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/wta/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Book Stop Project Location: Manila, Philippines Date Designed: 2016
Date Completed: 2016
Size: 12 sqm
Client: -
Programme: Education ABOUT WTA Architecture and Design
WTA Architecture and Design Studio is one of the Top 10 Architectural Firms in the Philippines in 2018 as cited by BCI Asia. It is a multidisciplinary group of young and idealistic architects, interior designers, urban planners and engineers based in Manila, Philippines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAA Architects</title>
      <link>/post/saa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/saa/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: St Josephs’ Nursing Home Location: Singapore, Singapore Date Designed: - Date Completed: 2017 Size: 22,022 sqm Client: Catholic Welfare Services Singapore Programme: Healthcare ABOUT SAA Architects
SAA is a leading full-service architecture practice headquartered in Singapore. With over 50 years of design and built expertise, they are committed to the pursuit of excellence in the design and delivery of people-oriented architecture that connects communities with their urban environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Bite Design Studio</title>
      <link>/post/one_bite_studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/one_bite_studio/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Project House Location: Sham Shui Po/Wan Chai/Aberdeen, Hong Kong Date Designed: 2017
Date Completed: In Progress Size: Depending on Vacant Shop
Client: Private Programme: Institution ABOUT One Bite Design Studio
One Bite is a creative team of strategists, architects, designers, community outreach managers and event managers. Headquartered in Hong Kong with an office in Singapore, the firm has been involved in various architectural, interior design; art and pop-up installations; visual communication and social creative projects in Hong Kong and Southeast Asia since 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Participate in Design (P!D)</title>
      <link>/post/pid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pid/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Hack Our Play - St. James Church Kindergarten Location: Singapore, Singapore Date Designed: 2017 Date Completed: 2017 Size: 128 sqm
Client: St. James Church Kindergarten Programme: Public Space ABOUT P!D
Participate in Design (P!D) is a non-profit design, planning and educational organisation that provides their expertise in participa- tory design to help institutions in Singapore design community-owned spaces and solu- tions. P!D was founded in 2013 by founders, Jan Lim and Mizah Rahman with the vision to spread the ideas of participatory design across Singapore.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>