<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cultural Preservation on Social Architecture</title>
    <link>/tags/cultural-preservation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cultural Preservation on Social Architecture</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/cultural-preservation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DnA_Design and Architecture</title>
      <link>/post/dna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/dna/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Brown Sugar Factory Location: Xing Village, China Date Designed: 2015
Date Completed: 2016
Size: 1,230 sqm
Client: Government of Zhangxi Village, Songyang County
Programme: Culture ABOUT DnA_Design and Architecture
DnA_Design and Architect is an interdisciplinary practice engaged in public buildings, architectural planning, landscape design, and cultural institutions. The studio aims to address contemporary living environments in both physical and social at various scales. DnA_Design and Architecture has done many successful projects, including Brown Sugar Factory, Wang Jing Memorial Hall, Chinese Herbal Garden, and Toufu Factory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAUKIN Studio</title>
      <link>/post/caukin_studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/caukin_studio/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Naidi Community Hall Location: Vanua Levu, Fiji Date Designed: 2018
Date Completed: 2018
Size: 130 sqm
Client: Naqaqa Giving Foundation
Programme: Public Space ABOUT CAUKIN Studio
CAUKIN Studio approaches architecture as a tool of empowerment that every individual and community should have equal access to. The organisation’s take on social architecture seeks to create better quality spaces for marginalised communities by minimising the economic barriers involved in the undertaking of such projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>studio-L</title>
      <link>/post/studio_l/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/studio_l/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Hajimari Art Center Location: Inawashiro, Japan Date Designed: 2013 Date Completed: 2014 Size: 1,217.14 sqm (Site area), 235.66 sqm (Building area), 284.01 sqm (Total floor area) Client: Asaka Hospital Group Programme: Culture ABOUT studio-L
Studio L is a Japanese firm that focues on community design. As community designers, the firm focuses on empowering the local people to participate in problem solving in their neighbourhoods. A typical workflow of a project consists of researching on case studies, conducting interviews and workshops as well as connecting different people in the local community to be involved in the project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>